<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>


	<!-- Incident Letters -->
	<WMH_Basilisk_LetterText>has reported missing caravans traveling through the area. Witnesses report that the area is a Basilisk hunting ground.\n\nContrary to popular belief, basilisks cannot turn anything to stone with their gaze, however, their acid, venom, claws and teeth provide them many other ways to kill. Several Glitterworld universities proclaim that a Basilisk's venom is the most potent across the rimworlds.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a Draconid, Basilisk can move over difficult terrain with ease.\n\n</WMH_Basilisk_LetterText>
	<WMH_Bearofleet_LetterText>put out a contract for a Bearofleet - an insane monstrosity devouring everything in the area. The only proof of its existence are several victims who managed to escape alive, only to die weeks later due to their gluttonous psychosis.\n\nBearofleets are genetic monstrosities created by the hubris of man. They were created by advanced genetic splicing of Aerofleet and Bear genetic material, and released into the wild, where their voracious appetite has proven to be a real challenge for small settlements. Their very presence instills a preternatural hunger in those who witness its bloated belly.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a Relict, Bearofleet contract provides much higher rewards.\n\n</WMH_Bearofleet_LetterText>
	<WMH_Chort_LetterText>is struggling with a Chort - a creature that destroys outposts, devouring anything that can be devoured, including rice, if it is available, but also extending to poultry, pork, the family dog and then the family itself.\n\nChorts are the somewhat smaller kin of fiends. They fight with little finesse, running straight towards their opponent and trying to knock him to the ground with the force of their charge. If surrounded by enemies, Chorts often use their third eye to throw an enemy into a berserk rage, making him turn on his allies.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a Relict, Chort contract provides much higher rewards.\n\n</WMH_Chort_LetterText>
	<WMH_Cyclops_LetterText>has been attacked by a Cyclops, leaving a wake of mutilated, crushed corpses and half-eaten livestock.\n\nCyclopses can easily be recognized by the single eye located in the center of their foreheads. If for some reason that is not visible, other tell-tale signs are their enormous size and incredible strength. They are often seen throwing heavy boulders at their enemies.\n\nMonster class traits: Being an Ogroid, Cyclops can regenerate wounds quickly in combat.\n\n</WMH_Cyclops_LetterText>
	<WMH_Djinn_LetterText>tried to capture and use the power of a Djinn, a powerful air elemental. Now all that is left of this settlement is a pile of rubble and corpses. The people put out a contract to hunt the monster down.\n\nA djinn is a powerful air spirit, a condensation of the power of that element endowed with consciousness and character - the latter usually nasty. According to researchers, a Djinn can attack with a continuous stream of energy, capable of taking down ultratech gunships with ease.\n\nMonster class traits: Being an elemental, Djinn is immune to fire and cold.\n\n</WMH_Djinn_LetterText>
	<WMH_Ekimmara_LetterText>reports several torn to pieces victims with characteristic bite-like marks - not on their necks, but on their whole bodies. Clearly a work of Ekimmaras.\n\nEkimmaras are not, despite what village gossips might say, intelligent vampires. They are instead infected travelers trapped in a monstrous body, who have no particular feelings about garlic, holy water or religious symbols.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a Cursed One, Ekimmara bite infection leads to full transformation and should be treated as soon as possible.\n\n</WMH_Ekimmara_LetterText>
	<WMH_Fiend_LetterText>has been attacked by a Fiend, a mountain of muscle and anger. They usually avoid human contact, but when hungry or endangered, they kill without difficulty.\n\nFiend is a walking mountain of muscle capped with horned, tooth-filled head. Is enormous size and strength allows it to take on an entire raiding party, whilst the third eye located in the center of their forehead is used to draw their prey into a state of hypnosis.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a Relict, Fiend contract provides much higher rewards.\n\n</WMH_Fiend_LetterText>
	<WMH_Fleder_LetterText>has been struggling with a small pack of Fleders, hunting at night for anything that moves in the area.\n\nFleders are lesser vampires, weaker than the rest of their ilk in almost every aspect. These vampires mainly fight with their teeth and claws, flailing them blindly and not stopping even when their victim is already dead.Their claws can rip through armour and flesh alike.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a Cursed One, Fleder bite infection leads to full transformation and should be treated as soon as possible.\n\n</WMH_Fleder_LetterText>
	<WMH_Fogler_LetterText>has lost several hunting parties in a dense fog surrounding the local area. All clues point to a family of Foglers.\n\nFoglers have powerful arms and claws like genetically engineered megaspiders, yet what makes them truly dangerous is their mastery of deception, beguilement and disorientation. When in danger, a fogler will release a dense cloud of smoke, making all the ranged attacks unsuccesful.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a necrophage, Fogler's attacks have a very high infection chance.\n\n</WMH_Fogler_LetterText>
	<WMH_Ghoul_LetterText>has reported a group of flesh-eating Ghouls, eating anything that even remotely resembles human flesh.\n\nGhouls are hard to describe. In part, they resemble humans - yet on the whole, they are the utter negation of all that is human. They are driven by one thing and one thing only: an insatiable craving for human flesh. Their repulsive look makes people vomit on sight.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a necrophage, Ghoul's attacks have a very high infection chance.\n\n</WMH_Ghoul_LetterText>
	<WMH_Golem_LetterText>has lost its raiding party to a large monstrosity made out of stone, nearly indestructible using conventional weapons. A contract on a Golem has been given to you, if you choose to accept it.\n\nGolems are mindless matter brought to life by psychic anomaly. Golems use no weapons, for they have no need – their fists, weighing over a hundred pounds each, can crush solid granite with one hit. Their solid rock armor can deflect almost every attack - killing a golem involves slashing a solid rock.\n\nMonster class traits: Being an elemental, a Golem is immune to fire and cold.\n\n</WMH_Golem_LetterText>
	<WMH_Hym_LetterText>has undergone its third election in the last two weeks, with all the previous leaders commiting suicide. A contract has been given to take care of the Hym tormenting these people.\n\nHym avoids sinking its claws into their victims. Instead, it saps their strength directly, through inflicting suffering. Speaking in a voice only the victim hears, Hym drives him to commit acts of violence, aggression and self-harm. Those tormented by a Hym are incapable of restful sleep weeks after the Hym is gone.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a Spectre, Hym instill fear in nearby humans, directly affecting their mood.\n\n</WMH_Hym_LetterText>
	<WMH_KikimoreQueen_LetterText>is unable to send out any caravans or hunting parties due to a large nest of Kikimores nearby.\n\nKikimores form colonies, making them similar to communal insects such as megaspiders. A kikimore colony is ruled by a queen and organized into something of a social hierarchy. Queen's bite injects paralysing venom whilst her chitin armor makes her almost immune to attacks.\n\nMonster class traits: Being an Insectoid, Kikimore queens always appear with other members of their species.\n\n</WMH_KikimoreQueen_LetterText>
	<WMH_Leshy_LetterText>has found several mutilated corpses, entangled within the roots and branches of trees and shrubs. All signs point to a Leshy, a god of the forest.\n\nLeshy, being called an Archotech failed creation, uses its inborn psychic ability to control the plants and animals within its territory. When a trespasser is found, Leshy can summon packs of manhunting animals. Always staying away from the enemy, Leshy can throw projectiles of pure psychic energy.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a Relict, Leshy contract provides much higher rewards.\n\n</WMH_Leshy_LetterText>
	<WMH_Nekker_LetterText>is reporting missing caravans and slaughtered livestock. All clues point to a nest of Nekkers.\n\nA lone nekker is harmless. Five are dangerous. Ten can kill even a veteran of the Mechanoid wars. Nekkers always attack in groups and by surprise. Nekkers are cowards, which means they will try to run if facing grave danger.\n\nMonster class traits: Being an Ogroid, Nekker can regenerate wounds quickly in combat.\n\n</WMH_Nekker_LetterText>
	<WMH_Werewolf_LetterText>put out a contract for a small pack of Werewolves hunting down poor enough farmers and travellers in the local area.\n\nNeither animal, nor man, the Werewolf takes the worst from both species: the bloodlust and primal nature of a timberwolf, and the ruthlessness and cruelty of a human. Feared by the tribal elders, Werewolves are nearly unkillable due to their fast wound regeneration.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a Cursed One, Werewolf bite infection leads to full transformation and should be treated as soon as possible.\n\n</WMH_Werewolf_LetterText>
	<WMH_Wraith_LetterText>has recently restricted entrance to their mass graves site due to bizzare lights and screams of torment. All clues point towards a group of Wraiths.\n\nWraiths suffer endless, indescribable pain. Filled with anger and a sense of having been wronged, they both envy the living and brim with overwhelming hatred for them. Their strong claw attacks can take out even the sturdiest of knights.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a Spectre, Wraith instill fear in nearby humans, directly affecting their mood.\n\n</WMH_Wraith_LetterText>
	<WMH_Wyvern_LetterText>is losing livestock on a daily basis due to the apex predator of rimworlds - a Wyvern.\n\nWyverns are often mistaken for dragons, and, though they are much smaller than their more famous kin and do not breathe fire, they are likewise extremely dangerous monsters. Before charging to combat, wyverns tend to spit acid at their enemies.\n\nMonster class traits: Being a Draconid, Wyvern can move over difficult terrain with ease.\n\n</WMH_Wyvern_LetterText>
	<WMHAux_Uwutross_LetterText>says "murrrr, rawrrrr x3. Nuzzles your wolgy bolgy". What?? Something must be wrong with the transmission... Perhaps some weird, antinatural phenomenom is affecting them?\n\nShould we go and investigate?\n\n</WMHAux_Uwutross_LetterText>
	

	<!-- Misc -->
	<WMH_DisableEvents>Disable all monster events (this efectively disables the mod)</WMH_DisableEvents>
	<WMH_GloryMode>Glory Mode (you are not prepared)</WMH_GloryMode>


	<!-- Hunt completed -->
	<WMH_LetterLabelDefeatAllMonstersQuestCompleted>Hunt completed</WMH_LetterLabelDefeatAllMonstersQuestCompleted>
	<WMH_LetterDefeatAllMonstersQuestCompleted>You have succesfully completed the monster hunt!\n\nThe payment from {0} has arrived, and faction relations have improved by {1}.</WMH_LetterDefeatAllMonstersQuestCompleted>
	<!-- Misc -->


	<WMH_MonsterClass>Monster class</WMH_MonsterClass>

	<WMH_MonsterClass_CursedOne>Cursed One</WMH_MonsterClass_CursedOne>
	<WMH_MonsterClass_CursedOne_Description>Each Cursed One has a rare attack (usually bite) that spreads the curse. Curses act like infection - they can be cured, but upon reaching 100% they turn the pawn into that very Cursed One that infected him/her.</WMH_MonsterClass_CursedOne_Description>

	<WMH_MonsterClass_Draconid>Draconid</WMH_MonsterClass_Draconid>
	<WMH_MonsterClass_Draconid_Description>Draconids avoid terrain path cost. They can move over stone chunks, barricades, trees, rivers like it's nothing.</WMH_MonsterClass_Draconid_Description>

	<WMH_MonsterClass_Elemental>Elemental</WMH_MonsterClass_Elemental>
	<WMH_MonsterClass_Elemental_Description>Elementa are completely immune to super cold and super hot temperatures, as well as fully immune to fire.</WMH_MonsterClass_Elemental_Description>

	<WMH_MonsterClass_Insectoid>Insectoid</WMH_MonsterClass_Insectoid>
	<WMH_MonsterClass_Insectoid_Description>Insectoids always appear in swarms with a different types of insectoids.</WMH_MonsterClass_Insectoid_Description>

	<WMH_MonsterClass_Necrophage>Necrophage</WMH_MonsterClass_Necrophage>
	<WMH_MonsterClass_Necrophage_Description>Necrophages have a very high infection chance on all attacks.</WMH_MonsterClass_Necrophage_Description>

	<WMH_MonsterClass_Ogroid>Ogroid</WMH_MonsterClass_Ogroid>
	<WMH_MonsterClass_Ogroid_Description>Ogroids have a basic slow wound regeneration.</WMH_MonsterClass_Ogroid_Description>

	<WMH_MonsterClass_Relict>Relict</WMH_MonsterClass_Relict>
	<WMH_MonsterClass_Relict_Description>Relicts are Gallatross level threats, but yield significantly bigger rewards.</WMH_MonsterClass_Relict_Description>

	<WMH_MonsterClass_Spectre>Spectre</WMH_MonsterClass_Spectre>
	<WMH_MonsterClass_Spectre_Description>Wraith presence instills fear, which directly affects mood of your pawns. Get ready for mental breaks mid-battle.</WMH_MonsterClass_Spectre_Description>



	<WMH_QuestMultiplier>Monster quests rate multiplier (READ MOUSEOVER TOOLTIP)</WMH_QuestMultiplier>
	<WMH_QuestMultiplierTooltip>The frequency of the monster quests being offered is multiplied by this number (with a multiplier of 1, it is offered every between 20 and 40 days at random). Numbers below 1 decrease the time, while numbers above it increase it. Note that this event doesn't "replace" normal quests, it works independently.</WMH_QuestMultiplierTooltip>
	
	<WMH_Reset>Reset</WMH_Reset>	














</LanguageData>